

Nguyen Ngoc Hung

Front-end Developer

Date of birth: September 03, 1999

Gender: Male

Phone: 0327874131

Email: nguyenngochung.work@gmail.com

Address: Pho Vien, Bac Tu Liem District, Ha Noi , Viet Nam

Website: https://www.facebook.com/nguyenhunggpt

OBJECTIVE

Research, learn new technologies and accumulate a lot of work experience. Completed well the assigned tasks and to build a friendly working environment among colleagues. In the future, my goals are to become a Full Stack Developer.

EDUCATION

July 2017 - Present

HUMG UNIVERSITY

Major: Computer Networking

GPA: 3.0/4

WORK EXPERIENCE

Jan 2019 - Dec 2020

Freelancer

Front-end Developer Main responsibilities:

- Basic web front-end design with HTML, CSS, JavaScript.
- Join working groups that develop small projects.
- Completed the courses at: CodersX, F8 Official ...
- HUMG scientific research member: Object detection using YOLOv3

Jan 2021 - Present

Open Techiz Company

Front-end Developer

- Learn and research React JS, React Native, Redux, Redux-Saga
- Working with Ubuntu
- Participate in website project maintenance working with European customers
- Developing website projects with Japanese customers onsite in
- Tool: Ubuntu, Visual Studio Code, Postman, Figma, Smart Git, GitLab...

SKILLS

TECHNICAL

- HTML & CSS (HTML5, CSS3, SCSS, Bootstrap, BEM)
- JavaScript, TypeScript
- React JS (React Hooks)
- React Native (Basic)

- Redux, Redux Saga
- Python
- Linux (Ubuntu, Ubuntu server)
- Git (github, gitlab)
- Express JS (Basic)
- MongoDB (Basic)

PERSONAL ATTRIBUTES

- Ability to work independently or in groups
- Positive, logical thinking, have a sense of responsibility, teamwork spirit
- Can work in high pressure environment.

PROJECTS

Products Website

(7/2020 - 8/2020)

Customer	Personal
Description	- This is a website that sells products paid online by paypal
Team size	1
My position	Developer
My responsibilities	- Developer
Technologies used	- React, React Hooks, Express JS, Git, MongoDB, RESTful API, PayPal Developer, MongoDB Atlas Postman, SmartGit, Visual Studio Code.

AVATARIUM

(2/2021 - 6/2021)

Customer	Japan
Description	- This is a website to manage 3D images, booking, download images, connect friends
Team size	15
My position	Front-end Developer
My responsibilities	- Code tasks front-end - Responsive website - Communicate with design and back-end - Bug Fixing
Technologies used	- React, React Hooks, Redux, Redux Saga, SCSS, Git, RESTful API - Postman, SmartGit, Visual Studio Code, Vgate, Figma

DEMO PERSONAL PROJECT

- Products Website:

https://shop-nnh.herokuapp.com/

- Video Other Project:

https://youtu.be/izdp1lokT8E

https://youtu.be/rsoJ-kCHKqo

- Github:

https://github.com/hungdevv

INTERESTS

Reading new technology news Playing games Listening to music